陈成 Chen Cheng

Full Stack Developer in Shenyang, China

With over 7 years of experience in software engineering, I'm a senior full-stack developer specializing in Web & Mobile Development & Auto Test Engineering. I have completed many projects, including leading an engineering team to build an event management platform that has reached tens of thousands of users. I'm a warrior, passionate about finding the best path to get things done. I'm a perfect resource to help convert your idea into a working product.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Hengcheng Aviation Technology Co., Ltd

01.2020 - 12.2022

- Develop and maintain responsive web applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Implement front-end frameworks such as React and Angular to develop dynamic user interfaces.
- Develop native Android and iOS applications using Java, Swift, Flutter, React Native.
- Utilize Git and SVN to manage source code, enabling seamless collaboration with other team members.
- Collaborate with project managers, designers, and developers to ensure timely and high-quality delivery of projects.

Mobile Developer & Software Test Engineer

Sysmed Co., Ltd 01.2018 – 12.2019

- Lead the testing process from start to finish including creating test plans and test cases.
- Execute tests and report defects, utilizing tools such as JIRA and Git to track defects.
- Work collaboratively with the development team to prioritize and resolve defects.
- Perform manual, automated, and exploratory testing of web applications.
- Utilize Selenium to automate test cases and improve testing efficiency.

WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER

Automobile Parts Co., Ltd

02.2016 - 12.2017

- Offer technical advices and solutions for team such as Design and BA
- Using React Native, Flutter to create an iOS, Android apps
- Using React, Web-socket and relative techs to build the web view
- Improve user experience through technical way such like reducing code base, reducing http requests, and compatibility with each platform

EDUCATION

LANGUAGE

SHANGHAI JIAO TONG UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science 2012 – 2015

CHINESE: **NATIVE** ENGLISH: **FLUENT**

SKILLS

Languages

JavaScript, Typescript, PHP, Java, HTML, CSS, C#, Dart, Swift, Dart

Frameworks

Angular, Next.js, Express, Laravel, Spring Boot, ASP.NET, React Native, Flutter

Libraries/APIs

React.js, Node.js, Socket.IO, Web3.js, Vue.js